dear customer I am an ICICI Bank
representative and I'm going to take you
through an incredibly easy journey of
video kyc for your personal loan so
let's begin log in with the link which
you have received for video kyc on both
SMS and email before you open the link
please ensure that you are in a strong
Network area or have a good Wi-Fi
connectivity on your device also follow
a few instructions for smooth process
keep original pan card a blank paper and
a black pen for Signature along with you
while doing the video kyc
look into the camera while verifying the
details
while capturing the photo make sure
you're in a proper attire with white
background proper lighting and keep your
eyes open
do not show aadhar card or share your
aadhaar number during the call
also no third person should be visible
or audible during the call
now once you have opened the link you
will get an OTP through a SMS and an
email to log into the video kyc portal
after entering the OTP please click on
login then you will see a video kyc
option click on the same to initiate the
video kyc call after this you will see a
pop-up with video kyc instructions click
on OK the next screen will show you your
name and your pan number you will need
to enter your aadhar number and accept
the terms and conditions then click on
verify now only once and wait for the
aadhar OTP to be received on your
aadhaar linked mobile number please
avoid multiple clicks and ensure that
the mobile number linked to aadhar is
active as you will receive an OTP
triggered by uidai on it enter the OTP
and click on continue then your aadhar
photo and address will be fetched from
uidai please confirm that your address
details and current address as per the
application form are correct by ticking
after confirmation you need to click on
initiate video kyc button only once and
wait for the web page to load please
avoid multiple clicks
after initiation the system will connect
you to an agent request you to wait till
you connect to the agent when you are
connected to the agent you will see a
chat window and the agent will initiate
a two-way video call please accept it
when the video call starts the agent
will ask you to share your location and
other verification parameters
please note that you need to be in India
while initiating video kyc
the agent will guide you through the
rest of the process and that is your
video kyc Journey yes it's as simple as
that with ICICI Bank